<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Animal</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="name">animal name</string>
    <string name="detail">The world is full of wonders, waiting to be explored. From majestic mountains to pristine beaches, from ancient ruins to modern marvels, there is so much to discover. Traveling allows us to broaden our horizons, learn about different cultures, and create lifelong memories.

Imagine standing on the edge of a breathtaking canyon, feeling the wind against your face as you take in the vastness of nature\'s beauty. Or walking through narrow streets of an old city, surrounded by centuries of history and stories untold. Each destination has its own charm, its own unique experiences to offer.

Traveling is not just about the destinations; it\'s about the journey itself. It\'s about the people you meet along the way, the friendships you forge, and the moments that take your breath away. It\'s about trying new cuisines, learning new languages, and stepping out of your comfort zone.

Whether you choose to explore faraway lands or embark on a local adventure, traveling opens your eyes to the wonders of the world. It teaches you to appreciate the diversity and beauty that exists in every corner of our planet.

So pack your bags, embrace the unknown, and set off on an adventure. Let the world be your playground, and let your curiosity be your guide. There\'s a whole world out there waiting for you to discover it. Bon voyage!
    The world is full of wonders, waiting to be explored. From majestic mountains to pristine beaches, from ancient ruins to modern marvels, there is so much to discover. Traveling allows us to broaden our horizons, learn about different cultures, and create lifelong memories.

Imagine standing on the edge of a breathtaking canyon, feeling the wind against your face as you take in the vastness of nature\'s beauty. Or walking through narrow streets of an old city, surrounded by centuries of history and stories untold. Each destination has its own charm, its own unique experiences to offer.

Traveling is not just about the destinations; it\'s about the journey itself. It\'s about the people you meet along the way, the friendships you forge, and the moments that take your breath away. It\'s about trying new cuisines, learning new languages, and stepping out of your comfort zone.

Whether you choose to explore faraway lands or embark on a local adventure, traveling opens your eyes to the wonders of the world. It teaches you to appreciate the diversity and beauty that exists in every corner of our planet.

So pack your bags, embrace the unknown, and set off on an adventure. Let the world be your playground, and let your curiosity be your guide. There\'s a whole world out there waiting for you to discover it. Bon voyage!
    </string>
</resources>